JUAN DAVID NARVÁEZ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

La Plata/Buenos Aires | juand.devO@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am a full stack developer with 1 years of experience in web application development. I have solid skills in JavaScript, ReactJS, NodeJS, SQL and other key technologies. I have worked on a variety of projects, including developing applications for companies of all sizes. I am a results-oriented person with the ability to learn quickly. I also have effective teamwork and communication skills.

EXPERIENCE

Software development - Remote

December, 2022 - Current

Ataway, Buenos Aires

• I work on integration projects using Dell Boomi, while applying my skills in ReactJS, NodeJS and ExpressJS to develop high performance solutions in internal company projects and where e-commerce companies like MELI are involved.

Tutor Web Development, JavaScript, ReactJs - Remote

April, 2021 - Current

Coder House, Buenos Aires

• As a tutor at Coder House, I have the opportunity to guide and orient students throughout the course, providing help and clear explanations on the different topics.

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science

In progress

Universidad Nacional De La Plata, La Plata-Buenos Aires

Technology in Software Development

January 2014 - Abandoned

Universidad Del Valle, Buga - Colombia

CERTIFICATIONS

Full Stack Web Developer/ 700 hours of theory and practice June 2022 - January 2023 Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires

• Intensive training, where they provide you with the necessary knowledge to start programming, from the basics to an advanced level in technologies such as JavaScript, ReactJs, NodeJs, SQL, and more.

Front End Developer

March 2020 - January 2021

Coder House, Buenos Aires

• I learned how to create a website using the best practices of web design, working with HTML and CSS. In addition, I used programming languages with Javascript and React Js.

TECH SKILLS

- TypeScript, NextJs, ReactJs
- NodeJs, Express, SQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL
- GIT, Redux, TailwindCSS, SASS, GNU/Linux, VsCode

SOFT SKILLS

LANGUAGE

- Creativity
- Adaptability
- Autonomy
- Teamwork
- Communication
- English A2
 - · Spanish Native